http://www.stevenspointcountryclub.com/privacy-policy

Member Section
Privacy PolicyEffective Date: June 1, 2019This privacy notice discloses the privacy practices for Stevens Point Country Club and our website; http://www.stevenspointcountryclub.com. This privacy notice applies solely to information collected by this website, except where stated otherwise. Throughout this policy, please note that “website” and “lead ad” are treated as one. This policy will notify you of the following:•	What information we collect;•	With whom it is shared;•	How it can be corrected;•	How it is secured; and•	How to address concerns over misuse of personal data. Information Collection, Use and Sharing We are the sole owners of the information collected on this site. We only have access to/collect information that you voluntarily give us via email or other direct contact from you. We will not sell or rent this information to anyone. We will use your information to respond to you, regarding the reason you contacted us. We will not share your information with any third party outside of our organization, other than as necessary to fulfill your request, e.g., to ship an order. Unless you ask us not to, we may contact you via email in the future to tell you about specials, new products or services, or changes to this privacy policy. Your Access to and Control Over Information You may opt out of any future contacts from us at any time. You can do the following at any time by contacting us via the email address or phone number provided on our website:•	See what data we have about you, if any.•	Change/correct any data we have about you.•	Have us delete any data we have about you.•	Express any concern you have about our use of your data Registration In order to use this website, a user must first complete the registration form. During registration a user is required to give certain information (such as name and email address). This information is used to contact you about the products/services on our site in which you have expressed interest. At your option, you may also provide demographic information (such as gender or age) about yourself, but it is not required.Orders We request information from you on our order form. To buy from us, you must provide contact information (like name and shipping address) and financial information (like credit card number, expiration date). This information is used for billing purposes and to fill your orders. If we have trouble processing an order, we'll use this information to contact you.SharingWe partner with another party to provide specific services. When the user signs up for these services, we will share names, or other contact information that is necessary for the third party to provide these services. These parties are not allowed to use personally identifiable information except for the purpose of providing these services.Security We take precautions to protect your information. When you submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and offline. Wherever we collect sensitive information (such as credit card data), that information is encrypted and transmitted to us in a secure way. While we use encryption to protect sensitive information transmitted online, we also protect your information offline. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (e.g. billing or customer service) are granted access to personally identifiable information. The computers/servers on which we store personally identifiable information are kept in a secure environment.Cookies We use "cookies" on this site. A cookie is a piece of data stored on a site visitor's hard drive to help us improve your access to our site and identify repeat visitors to our site. For instance, when we use a cookie to identify you, you would not have to log in a password more than once, thereby saving time while on our site. Cookies can also enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance their experience on our site. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information on our site. Some of our business partners may use cookies on our site (e.g., advertisers). However, we have no access to or control over these cookies.Links This web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the content or privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of any other site that collects personally identifiable information.Surveys & Contests From time-to-time our site requests information via surveys or contests. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and you may choose whether or not to participate and therefore disclose this information. Information requested may include contact information (such as name and shipping address), and demographic information (such as zip code, age level). Contact information will be used to notify the winners and award prizes. Survey information will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the use and satisfaction of this site.If you feel that we are not abiding by this privacy policy, you should contact us immediately via telephone at 715-34508900 or via email at gm@stevenspointcountryclub.com.
Memberships
Back to Top
Privacy Policy
Employment Opportunities
Stevens Point Country Club, 1628 Country Club Drive, Stevens Point, WI, 54481, United States715-345-8900gm@stevenspointcountryclub.com
Oliphant Golf Management 2020
Member Login
Welcome, (First Name)!
Forgot?
Show
Stay Logged In
Log In
Enter Member Area
(Message automatically replaces this text)
OK
My Profile
Not a member? Sign up.
Log Out
